I have an announcement to make here.
I, Sei Fukumura, have decided the date of my graduation.
It will be on November 29th.
The place,
Yokohama Arena.
Thank you very much.
Yes, okay.
And I will make an announcement in MC5,
Fukumura's graduation performance has been decided.
It will be at Yoga Marina on November 29th.
Wow.
January 29th.
It's looking good.
Feeling good.
Good Clothes Day.
And we will have another performance on November 28, the day before.
Two rows of horizontal sea.
Wait a minute.
I'm surprised.
Now?
From now on, Fukumura's graduation performance.
5?
Fukumura-san, you're announcing now too?
I know.
I just had my clothes taken.
I'm sorry. You were nervous about me.
I am nervous.
That's great.That's great.
So day 1 and day 2 are different.
Day 1 was special.
Day 2 is the second day of Sanctuary.
Wow!
It's amazing.
It's so good.
It's so cool.
Wait a minute.
Time is up.
I know, there was a huge time difference, right?
But I'm glad we can do 2days.
Thank you very much.
And the title is different, which means the content is also different.
I hope we can make it as exciting as possible,
We have less than two months to go.
That's great!
What?
Less than two months.
You're graduating?
Yes, I am.
Yay! Yes!
We are doing it.
So, even though we just started out with 14 members,
I hope we can bring Morning Musume。 I'll do my best.
I will do my best. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel.
This is Yuho Kami Ogura and Goikata Shimoita from Angulum, and this time we will be presenting with these two, so please bear with us until the end.
I'm 17 years old, a sophomore in high school from Okayama Prefecture, and I'm Shimobata ni Ikoi, the newest member of Angulum.I'm 17 years old, a second-year high school student from Okayama prefecture, and I'm the newest member of Angulum, Shimoita ni Igoe.
I've recently been studying sign language, so I'd like to introduce myself in sign language.
I'm 17 years old, a sophomore in high school from Okayama Prefecture.
I'm 17 years old, sophomore in high school, from Okayama, Japan.
I see you are studying sign language, but I think it's wonderful that you are getting more opportunities to let people know about you like this.
It's been a few months since Yukiho joined our group and it's been quite a while since she made her debut.
I'm having a good time. What do you enjoy?
I've learned a lot from the summer tour.
I was happy to be able to feel a little bit that this is how Angulum has come to be.
I was so happy to be able to feel how Angstrom has come to be.
I was really looking forward to seeing you guys in the future.
Thank you very much. Let's keep up the good work!
Now, Angulum Concert Tour 2023 Autumn, 11 members of Angulum is now underway.
This is the first tour where Yukiho and Hana Goto will be joining us in full force.
How do you feel about it?
Well, as the title of the tour says, there are 11 members of Angstrom, so each one of us will be in the spotlight.
I'd like to do my best to make the most of my individuality.
I could see a lot of their personalities at the rehearsal, so I really hope that everyone who is coming to the show is looking forward to it.
Please take a look at this video.
My name is Nikyo Shimoita.
Yes, this is the first day of the tour,
Thank you very much.
I have learned a lot of things from my seniors,
I want to do my best to make it clear,
I hope to be able to listen to everyone's voices at the same time,
I hope to be able to listen to everyone's voices while I'm doing my own work, and at the same time, to listen to the signals simultaneously.
I will do my best.
I will do my best,
I would like to improve my efforts to the songs and to the choreography.
Yes, I hope to perform better than I did last week.Yes, I hope I can perform better in my role last week than I am doing now.
I am Gohara.
The fall tour has started.
It's the first day,
I am very nervous, anxious, and also looking forward to it,
I have a lot of feelings,
I will do my best.
What do you want to do throughout the tour?
I want to do my best, both in terms of dancing and singing,
I want to do what I can't do now in terms of dancing and singing, so that I can do it perfectly by last week,
I want to improve my skills and performance level more and more,
I would like to improve my skills and performance level.
Let's begin.
It's the first day.
Here it comes. The first day of the fall tour.
This is the first time for both of us to perform with Mr. Chat,
We've had a lot of rehearsals,
Nakano, you're early.
Yes.
Absolutely.
Cute girl.
Her eyes are crumbling.
Pinch.
Pinchy.
So boring.
I know you are nervous,
Let's present ourselves properly to all of you.
Let's have fun.
Everyone, follow me, Kamiwaza, Tom, Leila, Rin, Kiro, Ume, Wakanyan, Rei, Yuupyon, and Harunan.Ladies and Gentlemen, Kamiwaza, Tom, Leila, Rin, Kilo, Ume, Wakanan, Rei, Yuupyon, Harunan, follow me.
Woooo!
Yay!
Please, please, please.
Please.
I'm off.
Please do. I'll do my best.
Please, please. I'll do my best.
Please do.
Yay! I'll do my best. Peace!
Ah a grain-wet mermaid who can't swim
Waves of even waves have come in, my heart shaking and bewildered
Struck by rain like autumn
The city is at the bottom of the sea
Fluctuating, clattering, drowning in tears
My good-bye won't stop, the bright red flowers are falling
Fluttering, fluttering, fluttering, I sent them motionless
Ah goodbye to the mermaid who can't swim
Your lines pierce my heart
Even the feet that stand still
I can't move, I can't move, I can't move, I can't stop my good-bye
Mermaid who can't swim
The landscape filled with memories
is consumed by sadness
snicy sitataru
One-piece wear grows old
in a zing, zing, zing, zing, zing, zing, zing, zing, zing, zing, freezing pace
I dreamed of when I was a child
All the heroines are strong
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkleTwinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
You can't do that, kid.
Ah Spoon ride Can't swim
Mermaid
Let the waves of loneliness fall
Embracing the heart that sways around
I could have faced you more back then
The gears were creaking, creaking, creaking
The shaking cogwheel I was running away because I was scared
Oh, sayonara to the mermaid who can't swim
I've been kissing you so hard, I've been confusing you
I'm so tall, I can't even stand on my own two feet.
Please, please, please
Ah, I long to swim
Who do you want to swim for?
Mermaid
Lost love sticks to me
Dull skies, if you let the light shine
Ah Honoway is on the horizon
I want to throw away my tears
I want to swim to a new dream
I can't go back to that sea
You are not here.
I like eggs. What do you like?
Moe and Yukiho are sending you the Angelem's Kamikogure and Shimoban, respectively, Halo! sta.
From here we would like to talk a little bit about each other.
I will ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo.
Yes, I'll do my best. I will do my best.
What surprised you the most when you joined Angelem?
The seriousness of the members.The member is serious.
Four months have passed since you joined. What was the most impressive event during this time?
Rockin Japan.
Tell us what kind of idol you are aiming for.
Love.
How did you get hooked on Hello!
Yes, I did. Let's see...Beyonce, the boy with glasses.
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year. What song would you like to perform on stage at least once?
I love Deaf Divas so much I feel like an idiot.
Oh, I got to hear a lot of them.
I got to hear parts of Yukiho that I didn't know about,
What was the most surprising thing for you after joining Angelem?
I've been watching you since I was a trainee,
I've been watching them since I was a trainee, when I watched them on YouTube,
I had an image of you as a messy person when I saw you on YouTube and so on,
But I was surprised by your attitude toward the stage.
Attitude?
Your posture was very serious and you seemed to be determined to do your best,
I was really surprised to see that.
It's true that the current Angelem has a very active on/off schedule.
And what kind of idol do you aspire to be?
Yes, that's right.
This is,
Love.
I love Angelem just as you love us,
And I want to deliver that love to the people who are watching us.
It's wonderful.
Then I feel like an idiot because I love the song I want to perform on the last stage so much.
Yes, I do.
It's a nice song.It's a good song.
It's a very good song.
What kind of performance do you want?
I want to wear a gold fluttering costume like our seniors,
Just like our seniors.
I would like to sing it on stage.
But I have an image of Yukiho-chan's performance as being glitzy,
That's right. So I thought to myself that it would be really cool.
Thank you very much.
Questions for Ms. Kamiokuriho will come after the VTR.
Hello! Ste.
Tsubaki Factory "It's my life!
Tsubaki Factory "If you're only delusional, you're free!
Tsubaki Factory "But I don't mind" Now on sale!
Hallo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Kamiokuriho from me. I'll do my best!
What has changed since you became the leader? Nothing!
If you were to give a catchphrase to Angulum, what would it be?
Eleven happy friends.
What are you interested in this fall/winter makeup?
Rather than fall/winter makeup, I would like to try Halloween makeup, which is very dark.
That would be nice.
What do you want to do this fall?
I like her flowers, and I want to go to a place where they are beautiful.
What song from Hello! Project's history would you like to record with your own voice?
Aya Matsuura's "Egao" (Smile).
It's nice.
Thank you very much.
Was there one that caught your attention?
It's good.Good.
I asked the first one. Are you saying that nothing has changed since you became leader?
There isn't. There are some things, but I don't have such a deep story to tell,
I feel that I am still able to be as I am because I am supported by the members and they support me a lot,
I am able to work without thinking too much about it.
One more thing,
Ah! The flower of longing!
Kanganbana! That's right. It's my favorite flower,
There is a beautiful place in Saitama Prefecture.
I went there last year, and I will definitely go there again this year.
There are so many flowers near my house.
Is that so? In Okayama Prefecture.
Yes, it is.
It's nice.
The place I want to visit the most is my parents' house, Yukiho-chan's house.
Thank you very much. By all means.
I wish I could go there once.
Please come.
Yes, I would. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I am Masashi Natsuyaki. I am Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 I am Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 I will do my best to complete the project this time, too.
Now, teacher, what would you like to make this time?
Today we will make pasta and pescatorre.
We will make pescatorre.
Yes!
Then let's do our best to make it delicious.
Please do.
So much I don't have to teach you.
You're doing it, pretty much. With your mother.
It's the first time you're making pescatorre.You are making pescatore for the first time, right?
Yes, I am.
That's great! It's open.
That's great!
So, where do we start this time?
Yes. I'd like to start boiling the pasta.
Yes. It's boiling perfectly.
Yes, it is. Let's get started.
I wonder how they do that.
Good job!
That was pretty cool!
Very cool!
I've never done that before in my life!
It's amazing!
Would you like me to chop the parsley first?
Yes!
I mean, you could use all the parsley if you wanted to, but...
It's like coarsely chopped.
If you grind it too hard, it will get crushed.
You want to chop it quickly.
Quickly!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes!
And then I'm going to have you put this back in here.
I'm gonna put it back in, okay?
Okay.
Wow! Looks so good!
I'm going to be cooking for a while.
Project's 25th anniversary the other day.
Project's 25th anniversary concert at YoyogiYou held a live concert in Yoyogi.
How was it in a word?
You can't sum it up!
Tears!
What was it like?
The daytime show on September 10 was a great experience for me.
I finally got to see my seniors in person, whom I had not been able to see in person.
I also got to see Mr. Nakazawa bursting into tears of frustration as he sang.
Wow! I could finally see them! I was so moved.
Yes, indeed!
There were tears, too.
And at that night's performance, I cried because I was so happy to see my seniors who have really helped me
I cried because I was so happy to see them singing again.
That's right!
Pasta time was over.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I'm in the middle of something.
I'm just now getting the water from the boiler.
It's very important, isn't it?
It's important. It's important.
Hurry up and mix it up. Let it come in.
Here it comes! It's coming in! It's the most important part of pasta.
They're both important.
I wanted to talk about something important.
Well, I'll leave it at that.
I want the noodles to be firm and tasty.
Is the heat still on?
Turn off the heat.
I'll turn it off.I'll stop, yes.
Oh, it's delicious!
Oh, really?
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
But there's still a little bit of core left.
You want some more?
No, I'm good.
Oh, okay?
Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Now that's some salt.
I know.
It's very important.
That's great!
Important, important, important!
Okay, I'll go to the noodles.
Yes, sir.
You don't need to light it.
No, it's still good.
Here, mix it.
Stir.
It's mixed, right?
Yes, here we go
Here, yes, yes, here
Point point point
Let the pasta absorb the juices.
Yes, it's important.
I see.
I see.Yes, sir.
Give me some of that juice.
Yes, sir.
The pasta will soak up more and more of it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Let it soak up some of the liquid.
Let it soak in.
Yes, yes.
And the core that was left over.
And the core that was left here...
Yes, yes, it will soften.
But then you realize that the 25th anniversary
We're all going to be able to celebrate together.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's amazing.
It's the path that our predecessors saved us from.
That's...
Yeah.
I'm really grateful.
And it's going to be handed down to the next generation.
That's true.
I have to pass it on, too.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
But please keep your eyes on me.
Of course.
I'll be watching you.
Okay.
Is that okay?And you're okay with that?
You've smoked enough.
Enough.
That's good.
It's good. I feel like I'm getting some kind of halo feeling.
Sure, sure.
I think it's good.
The light looks better than before.
Yeah, yeah, it's shining.
But if I really talk about the 25th anniversary.
I can't stop talking about it.
It's never ending, is it?
That's what I'm thinking.
I'm sure each one of us has our own thoughts and feelings.
I felt it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Even now, it's probably totally different.
I'm sure it depends on the age
I'm sure it's different depending on the age.
It's nice.
Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
It's been about 3 months or so.
And now that they've experienced the 25th anniversary...
It's not so bad.
You probably don't understand the gravity of the situation.
The gravity of the situation.
You want to understand, but you don't, do you?
No, you don't.
You can't.I can't finish it.
So when it's five years from now...
I'd like to see you regret it.
That's right.
I didn't understand the importance of Japan.
And that backyard...
I really...
It reminds me of the time when we were active members.
We would take pictures of each other.
It's like...
I can't help but cry just watching that scene.
It's like I'm moved to tears.
It's almost like we're going together.
Almost.
Yes.
How is it done?
It's done.
It's great.
That's great.
So you want to put it on a plate?
I'm just going to serve it.
Yes, please.
How do I serve it?
Spin the noodles first?
Oh! Let's do it.
What do you mean? You mean like this?
So, say, "Eggs.
Pull the egg out.
From the side.from the side
And there you go.
Oh, I see.
Repeat that a couple of times.
Just like in the commercials and packages.
Wow!
Wow, beautiful! You're so good!
Perfect!
Now all that's left to do is
Plenty of it.
How do you want it?
Which way should I put the shrimp?
I think it's better if you can see the meat of the shrimp.
Tail up or tail down?
I think the tail should be on top.
Like this.
It's good, right?
And the octopus, just toss it with the pasta.
Like this.
Yes! That's right.
There's a little bit of heat.
When did that happen? It was in there when it was supposed to be in there.
Yes, it was.
Maybe it would look better if you put it in the middle.
You're right.
But I love the octopus on top.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It looks amazing.
Oh, I'm not touching it anymore.Oh, I'm not touching you anymore.
It's okay, isn't it?
Looks so good!
Pescatore is complete.
It's wonderful.
Looks delicious!
Pescatore is ready!
How did you like it, Hita?
I'm so happy that the pasta turned out even more gorgeous and fancy than I had imagined!
It's amazing!
I hope you'll try it soon!
Yay!
Bon appétit!
Yum! It's delicious!
Ooh!
My first impression of the taste was garlic.
I knew it!
Oh no!
It's almost like peperoncino.
Yes, yes.
But, the noodles had absorbed so much flavor from the shrimp and shijimi clam, so as you chewed it, you could taste the seafood flavor.
Ah. Do you feel like making it at home again?
Yes, it does.
Oh!
You said you don't usually make pasta.
Yes, I do. I had an image that it was more difficult. I had an image of pasta as more work. I thought it looked like a lot of work.
It was quicker than I thought.
No, really. Probably because of Ishida-chan's deftness, the process went very smoothly this time.
It was quick.
I'm glad.It was good.
Things have already happened too fast.
It was fast, wasn't it? How did it go? Sensei.
I couldn't keep up with you at all.
No, it was amazing. I guess it's not that he swallows quickly, but he has the ability to get ahead of the others.
It was like he was leading everyone. I thought he was amazing.
He was pulling me along, too.
Yes, that's right. I am being utilized.
Thank you for saying that so nicely. I really appreciate your kind words.
If there is something you would like to try, I would be happy to have you try it here at Hello Kitchen.
I'd like to do it.
Yes, I would like to. That's all for now, Hello Kitchen.
Thank you very much.
I'm getting hungry.
I knew you are really good at cooking, Mr. Ishida.
Yes.
Do you cook, Yukiho?
I don't cook much,
I would like to make omu-rice someday.
I can make omelette rice.
But do you want the eggs to be fluffy or hard?
I like them firm rather than half-boiled.
Harder than half-boiled?
That's right. I like the kind my mother used to make.
She makes it for me.
But I have to learn how to make it from my mother.
I'll ask her how much she likes it cooked.
I, Kamiko, don't cook, you know.
But the dish I've made recently is steamed vegetables,
I don't know if I can say I made it,I don't know if I can say I made it,
I have one that can be made by cutting vegetables and microwaving them.
It is a simple dish that is steamed and eaten.
Do you have any recommendations on what vegetables to put in?
Recently, I've been putting in cabbage, bean sprouts, and the usual suspects,
Sweet potatoes?
It's delicious.
I would say steaming or steaming.
Yes, that's right.
It's seasonal.
Yes, they are.
So I'd like to eat a lot more in the future.
Hallo! STE.
With Mai Kamiokuriho of Angulum,
Mai Kamiokuriho of Angulum and Yukiho Shimoita of Shimoita. STE, presented by Mai Kamikuriho of Angulum and Yukiho Shimoban.
I'd like to introduce you to Yukiho a little more in depth.
Yes, I know.
So, I asked her manager about the episode about Yukiho Shimobata,
So, I will introduce some of them.
I will introduce some of them.
I'm curious. I'm curious.
Yes, I'm curious.
I wonder about Yukio-chan on the lower board.
Yes.
Like Hana Goto, she makes puns all of a sudden, so I'm having trouble with her.
Today, too, when I was introducing myself and talking about seiza, I was thinking of saying that seiza is gyoza (dumplings).
I've been getting a lot of "Oh, I'm a dumpling.
I love puns.
I love puns, don't you?The truth is, I love puns and stuff.
I love it.
I do.
Gyoza.
If it were most of them, I would say kuwakata.
Oh, I'm having trouble with my mood right now.
Ew.
I thought you would ask what type is yuppie.
It's kuwakata.
Ah. I'm glad you asked.
Next, let me tell you what impressed me about Yukio Shimoita.
This is a very cute, handwritten illustration of a photo that will be sold at the fall tour.
She said that I should pay attention to it because it is a very good drawing.
I'm so happy.
I also glanced at it earlier, and saw that you drew some animals.
Yes, I did. I did.
I'm not good at drawing, so I was amazed that you could draw such cute, fluffy illustrations.
That's right. But as you can imagine, I had to look at the animals to draw them, so I drew while looking at the animals.
Of course, it is autumn, so I draw autumn animals.
I see.
The first impression I got from spending time with Yukiho-chan on the lower board was that she was very energetic.
When I was talking with the members and Yukiho-chan came into the room, I felt that she was very energetic and energetic.
What is it? What is it? She really comes in with a bang.
Are you aware of it?
No, I'm not.
It's just that I'm spending a lot of time with her, and that's not all.
I sing and dance with a lot of energy.
My dance teacher told me that I was so energetic that I had to take pictures too fast.
He told me that.
My impression of Yukiho's performance on the lower board was a large motorcycle.When I saw Yukiho's performance on my lower board, my impression of her was that of a large motorcycle.
Her singing and dancing were like, "Get on it!
Why not?
You're getting all welly.
That's right.
But it's rare to find a girl whose individuality is visible from the beginning.
That's why I thought it was so interesting.
It's the first time I've heard of her.
I'm sure you've learned a lot about Yukiho.
I'd like to say hello to you all again.
I'm Yukiho Shimobita-ni, a new member of Angulum.
I'll do my best to give a vigorous performance in the fall tour.
Don't get too comfortable.
Tonight is a new starting line.
I'm sure the future will shine brightly
Tonight is a new starting line
Because everything will feed the next
If it's you
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
You can be strong
Happy
ni
Happy ni ana
Yeah Yeah You should be so happy
You should be so happy
I still can't see it right awayStill can't see it right away.
I can't even laugh at the silly revelations with you guys.
It's time for the ending of the show, brought to you by Angstrom's Hairy Gimme You and Shimoban Gyakata!
How was your first mc? I was so nervous.
I could feel you were nervous and I was nervous too... and we were both gods.
I hope you can look back on it in five years.
I'm sure you'll remember your first love when you've become more relaxed.
It's easy to see the difference when you haven't read the script.
Well, we're currently holding the concert tour "11 no Angelem" for the autumn of 2023.
As the title "11 Angsturm" suggests, each one of us stands out from the rest.
And each one of us has a part that stands out, like our costumes.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
We were given plain clothes for the summer tour, but we were given the same kind of costumes as the members.
It's the first time for me to wear the same kind of costume as the members.
I'm really happy to see two new members.
I think the atmosphere has changed a lot with the addition of two new members, Gotei-chan and Hana Goto, but I think we will grow and do our best from here.
But from here on, we will continue to grow and do our best, so please continue to support us and give us your best.
Hello! Project members appear on the channel every week. Project members will be uploading new videos every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
And now, my companions were Moe Appel and Yukiho Shimobita from Angulum.
Bye bye!